

# **SOFIA BLOMGREN**

070-692 87 11 sofiablo@kth.se www.sofiablomgren.me

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm 27 years old and I grew up in Stockholm, Sweden. After high school I moved to Santa Barbara, California, where I studied photography and media for two years at college. Right now I'm on the last year of the masters program in Media Technology at KTH in Stockholm. I'm also freelancing as a photographer through my own business. I'm a positive person who likes to plan and coordinate things, something that I've practiced a lot through many of the experiences mentioned below. After graduating I want to work with user experiece and, eventually, project management.

### **EDUCATION**

M.Sc.Eng. Media Technology, M.Sc. Interactive Media Technology	2015-present
KTH Royal Institute of Technology Stockholm, Sweden	
B.Sc. Media Technology	2015-2018

KTH Royal Institute of Technology Stockholm, Sweden

### 2012-2014 Certificate of Achievement in Applied Photography

Santa Barbara City College Santa Barbara, CA, USA

## WORK EXPERIENCE

F	ast Travel Games	Spring 2020
	Master Thesis Student	
	Researching UX for hand motion tracking in VR.	

Ericsson Summer 2019 Summer Intern

Summer intern working with UI and UX design for a VR project.

## Sofia Blomgren Photography

Owner, Photographer & Videographer 2016-present My own business through which I take different freelance photo and video jobs.

## Rockfoto

### **Photo Editor** 2016-present

Rockfoto is a photo agency for concert photography. As photo editor, I work as a coordinator between clients, concert promoters and our photographers.

#### **Photographer** 2015-present

Rockfoto is a photo agency for concert photography. As photographer, I take photos at concerts and then deliver the photos to a tight deadline.

# **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

# Chapter of Media Technology, KTH

#### **Head of the Photo Committee** 2018-2019

The Photo Committee is a group for everyone at the chapter who's interested in photography. As head of the committee, I created events for its members and worked together with other committees at the chapter when they needed photographers.

#### **Project Leader of the Student Reception** 2018

I was one of three project leaders of the student reception at the chapter. Being project leader includes recruiting students to work during the reception, planning the whole reception and being main responsible during all reception events.

## Osqledaren, KTH

Media Producer Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As media producer, I create content for web and social media.	2018-present
Photo Editor	2016-2017
Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As photo	

editor, I was responsible for the photographers and illustrators on the editorial staff and I guided them through the creative process. I was also a part of the paper's project group.

### 2015-2016, 2017-2018 Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As

photographer, I took photos for articles that I was assigned and delivered to a deadline.